[
    {
        "question" : "The Indian Oil Company wants to supply LP gas to its customers for cooking at a lower price by minimizing its transport costs. What is the best means of transportation?",
        "answer" : ["Pipeline"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which mode of transport is most suitable to reach an island ?",
        "answer" : ["Water","Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Raw teakwood is to be exported from Malaysia to India in bulk. Which mode of transport would you recommend?",
        "answer" : ["Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Apotex, The Canada health care company, wants to deliver pharmaceuticals from Toronto to Mississauga (same country). What is the best transportation mode?",
        "answer" : ["Package Carrier"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "DHL ​Deutsche ​ wants to deliver parcels into its customer’s house in Hong Kong. Which mode of transport would you recommend?",
        "answer" : ["Intermodal"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "HP Inc. (formerly Hewlett Packard) wants to bring personal computers and printers to markets quickly. What is the best transportation mode?",
        "answer" : ["Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "______ is costly, but its speed may create savings because of lower inventory.",
        "answer" : ["Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which mode of transportation has the capacity to carry the maximum lot size?",
        "answer" : ["Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "______ is the mode of transportation that has the highest variability in the delivery time.",
        "answer" : ["Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "______ is the mode of transportation which is considered to be the least expensive.",
        "answer" : ["Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What mode of transportation is limited to specialized products such as liquid and gases?",
        "answer" : ["Pipeline"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What modes of transportation are best suited for the delivery of time-critical small packages?",
        "answer" : ["Package Carrier"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "The China Electronic Company wants to import 20-foot containers smartphones to the United States. What mode would you recommend?",
        "answer" : ["Air","Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ is the mode which is more expensive than rail but offers advantage of door-to door shipment and characterized by shipments of 10,000 pounds or more.",
        "answer" : ["TL"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ is suited for shipments that are too large to be mailed as small packages (more than 150 lbs, but less than half a TL).",
        "answer" : ["LTL"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What mode of transportation are ideal for heavy and low-value shipments?",
        "answer" : ["Rail"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ is the mode of transportation which varies depending on infrastructure but is a low cost alternative.",
        "answer" : ["Rail"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which mode of transportation is highly specialized and limited to liquid, gases, and solids in slurry forms?",
        "answer" : ["Pipeline"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ is selected when the value per unit weight and relatively high speed of delivery is an important factor.",
        "answer" : ["Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which mode of transportation provides the speed delivery, as well as reduced risk of damage, security, flexibility and ease of access but higher courier fees?",
        "answer" : ["Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Shippers use _____ for small and time sensitive shipments.",
        "answer" : ["Package Carrier"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ suited for bulk shipment of products.",
        "answer" : ["Rail", "Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ provides service according to a fixed time schedule and is not flexible for loading and unloading of goods at any place.",
        "answer" : ["Rail"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What modes of transportation are the cheapest but can carry billions of tons of cargo ?",
        "answer" : ["Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "The Melbourne company has just won a one year contract to move 5,000 cartons (each carton weighs 15 kgs) of standardized components to be welded into the electrical board of photocopier machines assembled in Hong Kong. Which is the preferred mode of transportation?",
        "answer" : ["Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "______ carry bulk cargo but confined to a more limited infrastructure.",
        "answer" : ["Rail"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "SMB in Germany, companies in the field of material handling, shipping goods to the Oregon want to reduce transportation cost. ​ What is the best transportation mode?",
        "answer" : ["Intermodal"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ allows the customer to cost-effectively manage shipments from start-to-end, ensuring optimum care and efficiency every step of the way.",
        "answer" : ["Intermodal"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Advantages of _____ is Cargo can be moved to any part of the world using multiple modes of transport.",
        "answer" : ["Intermodal"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What modes of transportation suited for distance less than 400km which carry more than 150 lbs?",
        "answer" : ["TL","LTL"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ offers huge carrying capacities, which can grow to fit your need that haven’t a fixed amount of space.",
        "answer" : ["Rail"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Reynolds metals company wants to supply alumunium foil from US to Europe quickly. Which mode of transport would you recommend?",
        "answer" : ["Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Iron ore companies of Canada are to be exported to the US for a huge portion and don’t worry about time. What is the best means of transportation?",
        "answer" : ["Water"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ designed for a specific purpose, used mainly to transport bulk quantities of gas and oil.",
        "answer" : ["Pipeline"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ shipment of freight, generally under 12,000 pounds that would not fill a truckload by weight or volume.",
        "answer" : ["LTL"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What modes of transportation offer the highest capacity for land transportation and is used for long distance but slowest land transportation method?",
        "answer" : ["Rail"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ movement of freight used when time is the essence, used for lower weight freight and fastest way to ship long distances.",
        "answer" : ["Air"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ the use of a variety of modes of transportation used in combination for the best use of the respective advantages of each mode.",
        "answer" : ["Intermodal"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which modes depend on infrastructure but cover long distance and bulk?",
        "answer" : ["Rail","Pipeline"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What modes of transportation are fast delivery and cost effective but have availability or capacity issues?",
        "answer" : ["TL","LTL"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "What modes of transportation have advantage of speed and flexibility for mode shift and reduction in door-to-door cost ?",
        "answer" : ["Intermodal"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ are the preferred mode of transport for online businesses such as Amazon.com and Dell, as well as for companies such as W.W. Grainger and McMaster-Carr that send small packages to customers.",
        "answer" : ["Package Carrier"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which mode of transportation is used primarily for petroleum and natural gas?",
        "answer" : ["Pipeline"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Serving a low density of customers at a long distance is best done using ____.",
        "answer" : ["Package Carrier"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Serving a medium density of customers at a medium distance with shipments of more than 10,000 lbs is best done using ____ .",
        "answer" : ["TL"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ offers point to point service over any distance, fast and reliable, low damages and lost rates with less than 150 pounds freight.",
        "answer" : ["Package Carrier"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ Unique mode of transportation as the equipment is fixed in place and the product moves through it in high volume.",
        "answer" : ["Pipeline"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "_____ use of two or more modes of transportation cooperating on the movement of a shipment by publishing a through rate.",
        "answer" : ["Intermodal"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Which kind of transportation service provider provides convenient door-to-door service between two locations and is capable of carrying most any form of freight?",
        "answer" : ["TL","LTL","Package Carrier"]
    },
    {
        "question" : "Serving a low density of customers at a long distance is best done using ____.",
        "answer" : ["Package Carrier"]
    }
]